Guide to the Larry Polansky Papers MSS.405
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI. Personal, 1937-ongoing; 16.25 Linear Feet in 33 manuscript boxes, 1 flat box, and 1 oversize flat box; 126 Gigabytes in 112,457 computer files.; 641 audiocassettes; 30 sound cassettes (dat); 1 websites in 1 archived website.
  - Knowles, Alison, 1998, undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - L -- Lowenberg, Richard, 1979-2012, undated (Box 49, Folder 1-10)
  - M, 1965, 1978-2009 (Box 49, Folder 11-12)
  - MacDowell Colony Application, 2009, 2012 (Box 49, Folder 13-14)
  - Mahler, David, 1984-2013 (Box 49, Folder 15-16, Box 50, Folder 1-9)
  - Mann, Chris -- Music Through Midi, 1976-2008, undated (Box 50, Folder 10-18)
  - N -- Pound, 1977-2009, undated (Box 51, Folder 1-16)
  - Polansky Colleagues' Music Sound Recordings on Digital Audio Tape (DAT), 1988-2002 (Box 103)
  - Pritchett -- Rockmore, 1970s, 1981-2013 (Box 52, Folder 1-10)
  - Rosenboom, D., 1969-1987, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 11-12)
  - Rothenberg, undated (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
  - Rudhyar -- George Russell "River", 1966-1985, undated (Box 53, Folder 3-5)
  - S, 1968-2010 (Box 53, Folder 6-8)
  - I Waygan Sadra -- Schoenberg, 1955-1999, undated (Box 54, Folder 1-7)
  - Scholz, Carter, circa 1993, undated (Box 54, Folder 8-10)
  - Seeger, Peggy -- Shaker Museum Letter, 1977-2000 (Box 54, Folder 11-16)
  - Shepard, Roger -- T, 1978-2011, undated (Box 55, Folder 1-14)
  - Sign, Flute Lessons, undated (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Sound Recordings on Audiocassette -- Senior Recital, Auditions, and Colleagues' Music, 1977-2000 (Box 98, Box 99, Box 100)
  - Tenney, [James], 1969, undated (Box 55, Folder 15-16)
  - Thanksgiving Booklet -- Barry Truax, 1975-1983, 2001, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 17-19)
  - Trubee, John -- Mike Winter, 1967-2010, undated (Box 56, Folder 1-13)
  - Christian Wolff, 1964-2011 (Box 56, Folder 14-15)
  - Workshop on Matlab -- York University Class..., 1959-1997 (Box 57, Folder 1-3)
  - Young, Gayle, 1984-2004 (Box 57, Folder 4-5)
  - Zipf's Law Stuff -- Richard Zvonar, 1975-2005, undated (Box 57, Folder 6-8)